

## BIRTHDAY:

19/06/1999

### **NATIONALITY:**

ITALIAN

### LICENCE:

B

### **ADDRESS:**

Via San Pio X 208 TV 31033 (ITALY)

### PHONE:

+39 389 290 3924

### **EMAIL:**

sergioallushaj@gmail.com

# SERGIO ALLUSHAJ

I specialize in front-end development with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Next js. My focus is on creating beautiful and functional websites with a modern look and excellent user experience. View my current projects on: https://kuroiokami89.github.io/Portfolio-Vantablack/

# **EDUCATION**

09/2013 - 07/2018

DIPLOMA: AUDIOVISUAL
PRODUCTIONS IPSIA GALILEO
GALILEI

I studied photography both technically and theoretically, learning the photographic language through cinema, art, and history. My training included professional videomaking, covering audio, video, and software equipment for diverse productions such as interviews, commercials, sports events, shows, and documentaries.

05/2023 - ONGOING

WEB DEVELOPMENT AND
DESIGNER COURSE,
ACCADEMIA DELLE
PROFESSIONI, PADUA, ITALY

Currently studying HTML5, CSS4, JavaScript, and jQuery for front-end development and using Figma to study responsive and user-friendly principles for web application prothotipying. Utilizing Photoshop, Illustrator and After Effects for design and animation tasks like personalized logos, icons and creation of video motions.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

2021/12 - 2022/08

### CUSTOMER SERVICE - STOREDEN (TV)

Dedicated technical assistance to customers in case of bugs on the Storeden e-commerce platform or on the website. Performed front-end customizations of websites using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Twig, and Bootstrap.

2022/12 - 2023/02

## JUNIOR BACK-END DEV - ESOSPHERA (RS)

Developed web applications with a focus on object-oriented programming using Yii2 as the main framework, and used Psql for relational databases.

2023/05-2023/10

## JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEV - W-EASY

Development and maintenance of websites and management services for companies using the following technologies: JavaScript HTML CSS and PHP.

"I authorize the processing of my personal data contained in the CV in accordance with art. 13 of Legislative Decree 30 June 2003 n. 196 - 'Code regarding the protection of personal data' and art. 13 GDPR 679/16 - 'European regulation on the protection of personal data'"

Castelfranco Veneto, 27/06/2024

Sergio Allushaj